Henry Y. Porter Theater Memorabilia Collection MS003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Artists and other celebrities; prints, photographs, and artifacts, 1722 -- 1990; 1880 -- 1920; MS003.001; 33.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - 19th century actors, singers and personalities, 8x10s mounted on cardstock, MS003.001.038
    - Jessie Bond, English singer and actress, (1853-1942), MS003.001.038.00025 (Box 38)
    - Marion Terry, English actress, (1856-1930), MS003.001.038.00026 (Box 38)
      Sister of Ellen Terry.
    - Kate Terry, English actress, (1844-1924), MS003.001.038.00027 (Box 38)
    - Sir George Alexander, English actor and theatre manager, (1858-1918), MS003.001.038.00028 (Box 38)
      aka: George Samson.
    - William Terriss, English actor (1847-97), MS003.001.038.00029 (Box 38)
      aka: William Lewin.
    - Sir James M. Barrie, Scotch novelist and dramatist, (1860-1937), MS003.001.038.00030 (Box 38)
      Wrote: "Quality Street," "The Admirable Cuchton," "Little Minister," "Peter Pan," "Alice-Sit-by-the-Girl," What Every Woman Knows," etc.
    - Henry Arthur Jones, English playwright, (1851-1929), MS003.001.038.00031 (Box 38)
      Wrote: "The Silver King," "Saints and Sinners," "The Tempter," "Mrs. Davies Defence," etc.
    - George Grossmith, English actor (1847-1912), MS003.001.038.00032 (Box 38)
    - Fanny Brough, English actress, (1856-1914), MS003.001.038.00033 (Box 38)
      aka: Mrs. Richard Smith Boleyn.
    - Mrs. Patrick Campbell, English actress, (1867-1940), MS003.001.038.00034 (Box 38)
      aka: Beatrice Stella Tanner.
    - Hermann Vezin, American actor, (1829-1910), MS003.001.038.00035 (Box 38)
    - Unidentified, MS003.001.038.00036 (Box 38)
      Man standing next to a plaque of The California Theatre.
  - "Broadway," 19th c. weekly gossip magazine, 1892-10-15 -- 1893-10-07; MS003.001.039.001 (Box 39)
    48 issues. (missing 4)
  - Oversize photographs of 19th c. to early 20th c. actors and singers, some signed, 1890 -- 1940; MS003.001.040.001 (Box 40)
    Some previously framed.
  - Autographed, hand-drawn pictures of famous personalities from photographs, 1897 -- 1902; MS003.001.041
    Many of them signed, unknown artists.
    - Julia Marlowe, signed, MS003.001.041.00001 (Box 41)
      Watercolor.
    - Unidentified, n.d, signature card included, MS003.001.041.00002 (Box 41)
      Picture of a man in long robe costume. Acrylic.
    - Unidentified, MS003.001.041.00003 (Box 41)
      Pencil drawing of an old man with long white beard. Signature card ripped off.
    - Unidentifed, signed, MS003.001.041.00004 (Box 41)
      Watercolor of a man in black costume.
    - Viola Allson, signed, MS003.001.041.00005 (Box 41)
      Watercolor and pencil.
    - Helena Modjeska, 1900; MS003.001.041.00006 (Box 41)
      Pencil drawing of her in a large hat.
    - Henry Irving, 1902; MS003.001.041.00007 (Box 41)
      Colored pencil drawing done by S. McLaughlin, 1891.
    - Jesse Bartlett Davis, 1897; MS003.001.041.00008 (Box 41)
      Watercolor of her in a black vail.
    - Manihan (?), 1897; MS003.001.041.00009 (Box 41)
      Watercolor and pencil in Juliet(?) costume.
    - Annie Russell, 1899; MS003.001.041.00010 (Box 41)
      Colored pencil.
    - Julia Arthur, n.d., signature card included, MS003.001.041.00011 (Box 41)
      Black watercolor, seated pose.
    - DeWolfe Hopper, 1897; MS003.001.041.00012 (Box 41)
      Pencil and watercolor.
  - Cabinet cards, postcards and cartes de visite of various theatre and musical personalities, some signed, some unknown, 1900 -- 1960; MS003.001.042.00001 (Box 42)
    Includes one each of Buffalo Bill, Jenny Lind and Tom Thumb and Lavinia Warren.
  - Signed postcards and 5x7s of female opera singers, sopranos and contraltos, 1907 -- 1968; MS003.001.043.001 (Box 43)
    Alphabetical.
  - Signed postcards and 5x7s of male opera singers, tenors and bass, 1909 -- 1966; MS003.001.044.001 (Box 44)
  - Cabinet cards and musical notation collector's cards of male and female opera singers, all signed, 1895 -- 1907; MS003.001.045.001 (Box 45)
    Not all with adjoining cabinet cards.
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra conductors and concertmasters, 8x10 photos and some letters, 1889 -- 1969; MS003.001.046
    - Adamowski, Timothee, Polish violinist (1858-1943), 1907; MS003.001.046.00001 (Box 46)
    - Arbas, E. Fernandez, Spanish conductor (1863-1939), 1928; MS003.001.046.00002 (Box 46)
    - Bernstein, Leonard, American conductor, composer, pianist (1918-), 1952; MS003.001.046.00003 (Box 46)
    - Burgin, Richard, Polish violinist (1892-1981), 1945; MS003.001.046.00004 (Box 46)
      Concertmaster.
    - Casella, Alfredo, Italian pianist and conductor, 1929; MS003.001.046.00005 (Box 46)
      2 images.
    - Dickson, Harry Ellis, American conductor (1908-), 1960; MS003.001.046.00006 (Box 46)
    - Fiedler, Arthur, American cellist and conductor (1894-1979), 1931 -- 1963; MS003.001.046.00007 (Box 46)
      7 images, one note to Porter from Fiedler.
    - Fiedler, Max, German conductor (1859-1939), 1934; MS003.001.046.00008 (Box 46)
      3 images and one letter from Fiedler to Porter.
    - Fradkin, Fredric, American violinist (1892-1963), 1925; MS003.001.046.00009 (Box 46)
    - Gericke, Wilhelm, Austrian conductor, (1845-1925), 1889 -- 1898; MS003.001.046.00010 (Box 46)
      2 images and one signed note.
    - Henschell, Sir Georg, German-British baritone, conductor and composer (1850-1934), 1889 -- 1935; MS003.001.046.00011 (Box 46)
      4 images (3 signed, one with Serge Koussevitzky), one notecard signed.
    - Hess, Willy, German violinst (1859-1939), 1904; MS003.001.046.00012 (Box 46)
    - Higginson, Henry Lee, founder of the BSO (1834-1919), MS003.001.046.00013 (Box 46)
    - Jacchia, Agide, Italian conductor (1875-1932), 1927; MS003.001.046.00014 (Box 46)
      2 images, one signed.
    - Kneisel, Franz, German conductor (1865-1926), MS003.001.046.00015 (Box 46)
    - Koussevitzky, Dr. Serge, Russian conductor (1874-1951), 1927; MS003.001.046.00016 (Box 46)
      10 images, one signed. Includes one of his wife, Olga Koussevitzky, and a typed, signed letter from him to a Mr. Howell Davis.
    - Leinsdorf, Erich, Austrian conductor (1912-1993), 1963; MS003.001.046.00017 (Box 46)
      Includes one signed 8x10 and a note from him to Porter regarding the photo.
    - Listemann, Bernhard, German violinist, conductor, teacher (1841-1917), MS003.001.046.00018 (Box 46)
      Signed cabinet card. Concertmaster.
    - Monteaux, Pierre, French conductor (1875-1964), 1918 -- 1923; MS003.001.046.00019 (Box 46)
      5 images, three signed.
    - Muck, Dr. Karl, German conductor (1859-1940), 1908; MS003.001.046.00020 (Box 46)
    - Munch, Charles, Alsatian conductor (1891-1968), 1952; MS003.001.046.00021 (Box 46)
    - Nikisch, Arthur, Hungarian conductor (1855-1922), MS003.001.046.00022 (Box 46)
      3 images, one signed.
    - Ozawa, Seiji, Japanese conductor (1935-), MS003.001.046.00023 (Box 46)
    - Paur, Emil, Czech conductor (1855-1932), MS003.001.046.00024 (Box 46)
      5 images, one signed. Includes two cabinet cards.
    - Rabaud, Henri, French conductor and composer (1873-1949), 1918 -- 1919; MS003.001.046.00025 (Box 46)
      2 images, one signed. Also includes a typed letter from him to a Mr. John K. Burgess.
    - Sanroma, Jesus Maria, Puerto Rican pianist (1902-1984), 1953; MS003.001.046.00026 (Box 46)
    - Silverstein, Joseph, American violinist (1932-), 1963; MS003.001.046.00027 (Box 46)
    - Steinberg, William, German conductor (1899-1978), MS003.001.046.00028 (Box 46)
      3 images unsigned.
    - Strube, Gustav, German conductor and violinist (1867-1953), 1933; MS003.001.046.00029 (Box 46)
    - Thomas, Michael Tilson, American conductor (1944-), MS003.001.046.00030 (Box 46)
    - Williams, John, American conductor and composer (1932-), MS003.001.046.00031 (Box 46)
    - Wilson, Charles, American conductor, 1969; MS003.001.046.00032 (Box 46)
      One image and a typed to letter to Porter.
    - Witek, Anton, Czech violinist (1872-1933), MS003.001.046.00033 (Box 46)
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra, Tanglewood audiences, MS003.001.046.00034 (Box 46)
      Tanglewood audiences and images of the whole symphony.
    - Unidentified letter to E. M. Stanford Esq., 1890; MS003.001.046.00035 (Box 46)
  - Postcards, 5x7s and 8x10s of male and female opera and musical personalities, unsigned, 1900 -- 1950; MS003.001.047.001 (Box 47)
    Broken down from Porter's albums. An inventory is available, though it does not follow exactly with the contents of the albums.
  - Political and cultural personalities, 8x10s, all signed, 1928 -- 1962; MS003.001.048
    Alphebetical, includes Henry Ford, Helen Keller and Theodore Roosevelt Jr.
    - Jane Addams, American social worker (1860-1935), signed, MS003.001.048.00001 (Box 48)
    - Senator William E. Borah (1865-1940), signed, MS003.001.048.00002 (Box 48)
      U.S. Senator from Idaho, 1907-40.
    - Harry F. Boyd, American politician (1887-1966), signed, MS003.001.048.00003 (Box 48)
      Governor of Virginia, 1926-30, Senator of Virginia, 1933-66.
    - Richard E. Byrd (1888-1957), American polar explorer, signed, 1928; MS003.001.048.00004 (Box 48)
    - Carrie Chapman Catt (1859-1947), American woman suffrage leader, signed, MS003.001.048.00005 (Box 48)
    - James B. Conant (1893-1978), signed, MS003.001.048.00006 (Box 48)
    - John N. Dempsey, Governor of Connecticut, signed, MS003.001.048.00007 (Box 48)
    - Everett M. Dirksen, U.S. Senator of Illinois, signed, MS003.001.048.00008 (Box 48)
      (1896-1969) Image is a copy of a drawing, not a photograph.
    - Frank Driden (?), signed, MS003.001.048.00009 (Box 48)
    - Harvey S. Firestone (1868-1938), American industrialist, signed, MS003.001.048.00010 (Box 48)
    - Henry Ford (1863-1947) American automobile industrialist, signed, MS003.001.048.00011 (Box 48)
    - Henry Ford II (1917-87), American motorcar manufacturer, signed, 1962; MS003.001.048.00012 (Box 48)
      Son of Edsel Ford, grandson of Henry Ford I.
    - Harry E. Fosdick (1878-1969), American clergyman, signed, MS003.001.048.00013 (Box 48)
    - Dr. Glen Frank, signed, MS003.001.048.00014 (Box 48)
    - Herbert Gelman, signed, MS003.001.048.00015 (Box 48)
    - Barry M. Goldwater (1909-98), signed, MS003.001.048.00016 (Box 48)
    - William Green (1873-1952), American labor leader, signed, MS003.001.048.00017 (Box 48)
    - Edgar A. Guest (1881-1959), American writer, signed, 1929; MS003.001.048.00018 (Box 48)
    - Gabriel Heathen, radio commentator, signed, MS003.001.048.00019 (Box 48)
    - Hiram W. Johnson (1866-1945), American politician, signed, 1929; MS003.001.048.00020 (Box 48)
      U.S. Senator from California 1917-45
    - Samuel Lusull (?), signed, 1935; MS003.001.048.00021 (Box 48)
    - Helen Keller (1880-1968), American author and lecturer, signed, 1938; MS003.001.048.00022 (Box 48)
      Blind and deaf since 19 months old.
    - Robert S. Kerr (1896-1963), American politician, signed, MS003.001.048.00023 (Box 48)
      Governor of Oklahoma 1943-47, U.S. Senator of Oklahoma 1949-63.
    - Robert M. La Follette Jr. (1895-1953) Ex-U.S. Senator, Wisconsin, signed, MS003.001.048.00024 (Box 48)
    - Fiorello H. La Guardia (1882-1947), Mayor of New York City, signed, MS003.001.048.00025 (Box 48)
    - William Lawrence (1850-1941) American Protestant Episcopal clergyman, signed, MS003.001.048.00026 (Box 48)
      Bishop of Massachusetts 1893-1926.
    - John L. Lewis (1880-1969), American labor leader, signed, MS003.001.048.00027 (Box 48)
    - John Lodge and Eugene Carver Jr. signed by both, 1929; MS003.001.048.00028 (Box 48)
    - Harford MacNider, signed, MS003.001.048.00029 (Box 48)
    - Thomas Mann (1875-1955), German author, signed, 1938; MS003.001.048.00030 (Box 48)
    - Bishop William Manning (1866-1949), signed, MS003.001.048.00031 (Box 48)
    - Frederick W. Mansfield, Mayor of Boston, 1937; MS003.001.048.00032 (Box 48)
    - Edwin Markham, American poet (1852-1940), signed, 1935; MS003.001.048.00033 (Box 48)
    - Robert B. Meyner, MS003.001.048.00034 (Box 48)
    - Glen Moritz (?), MS003.001.048.00035 (Box 48)
    - George William Norris (1861-1944), MS003.001.048.00036 (Box 48)
    - Lafford P., signed, 1928; MS003.001.048.00037 (Box 48)
      Unable to read last name.
    - Wesley Powell (1915-81) signed, MS003.001.048.00038 (Box 48)
      Governor of New Hampshire 1959-63.
    - Edwin Vernon Rickenbacker (1890-1973), WWI aviator, signed, 1929; MS003.001.048.00039 (Box 48)
      America's "Ace of Aces"
    - Albert C. Ritchie, signed, 1929; MS003.001.048.00040 (Box 48)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller (1908-79), politician and businessman, signed, MS003.001.048.00041 (Box 48)
      Governor of New York 1958-73, Vice President of the U.S. 1974-1977.
    - Theodore Roosevelt Jr. (1887-1944), politician, oldest son of Theodore Roosevelt, signed, MS003.001.048.00042 (Box 48)
      Governor of Puerto Rico 1929-32, Governor General of Philippines 1932-33. Served in WWI and WWII
    - David Sarnoff (1891-1971), American executive, signed, 1949; MS003.001.048.00043 (Box 48)
      Chairman of the board of directors of Radio Corporation of America.
    - Charles M. Schwab (1862-1939), signed, MS003.001.048.00044 (Box 48)
    - Stuart Symington (1901-88), signed, MS003.001.048.00045 (Box 48)
    - Norman M. Thomas (1884-1968), American politician, signed, MS003.001.048.00046 (Box 48)
      Socialist candidate for President 1928, 1932, 1936.
    - Robert F. Wagner (1877-1953), lawyer and legislator, signed, MS003.001.048.00047 (Box 48)
      State Senator 1909-1918, Supreme Court Justice, introduced the Wagner Act.
    - Stephen S. Wise (1874-1949), American rabbi, signed, 1937; MS003.001.048.00048 (Box 48)
    - Unidentified, signed, 1936; MS003.001.048.00049 (Box 48)
  - Opera singers and musical personalities 8x10s, male and female, 1915 -- 1970; MS003.001.049.001 (Box 49)
    Unsorted files of productions shots and portraits of singers such as Frances Alda, Earnestine Schumann Heink, Anna Fitzu, Eugene Conley, Theo Adam, Gladys Swarthout etc. A few of them are signed.
  - Various 8x10s of opera, musical and literary personalities, men and women, all signed, 1888 -- 1956; MS003.001.050
    Alphabetical, includes Jascha Heifetz, Oppenheim Phillips and Marguerita Sylva.
    - La Puma, Guiseppe, baritone, 1900 -- 1901; MS003.001.050.00001 (Box 50)
      As a character from Wagner opera, Die Walkure.
    - Althouse, Paul, American tenor (1889-1954), 1926; MS003.001.050.00002 (Box 50)
    - Althouse, Paul, American tenor (1889-1954), MS003.001.050.00003 (Box 50)
    - Apollo, Dave, MS003.001.050.00004 (Box 50)
    - Bispham, David, American baritone (1857-1921), MS003.001.050.00005 (Box 50)
    - Bispham, David, American baritone (1857-1921), 1927; MS003.001.050.00006 (Box 50)
    - Deryne, Fely, French soprano, MS003.001.050.00007 (Box 50)
    - Dickenson, Jean, singer, 1945; MS003.001.050.00008 (Box 50)
    - Empery, A.G. (?), 1918; MS003.001.050.00009 (Box 50)
    - Ferola, Nicola as Otello, MS003.001.050.00010 (Box 50)
    - Fursch-Madi, Emmy, French soprano (1847-1894), 1888; MS003.001.050.00011 (Box 50)
    - Heifetz, Jascha, Russian violinist, 1923; MS003.001.050.00012 (Box 50)
    - Gatti-Casazza, Guilio, Italian impresario (1869-1940), 1892; MS003.001.050.00013 (Box 50)
    - MacIntosh, Nancy, MS003.001.050.00014 (Box 50)
    - Marbrery, Elizabeth, famous concert manager, MS003.001.050.00015 (Box 50)
    - Meisle, Kathryn, American contralto, MS003.001.050.00016 (Box 50)
    - Nielsen, Alice et al. (1876-1943), MS003.001.050.00017 (Box 50)
      Taken by Eugene Cowles.
    - Unidentified as "Ophelia", MS003.001.050.00018 (Box 50)
    - Patti, Adelina (1843-1919), 1906; MS003.001.050.00019 (Box 50)
    - Phillips, Oppenheim, E. (1866-1946), MS003.001.050.00020 (Box 50)
    - Pons, Lily, MS003.001.050.00021 (Box 50)
    - Sapio, Clementine de Vere, French soprano (1865-1954), MS003.001.050.00022 (Box 50)
    - Sousa, John Philip, American bandmaster and composer (1854-1932), MS003.001.050.00023 (Box 50)
    - Sundelius, Marie, Swedish soprano, MS003.001.050.00024 (Box 50)
    - Sylva, Marguerita, at age 80 (1875-1957), 1956; MS003.001.050.00025 (Box 50)
    - Wicklow, Florence, American contralto (1882-1962), MS003.001.050.00026 (Box 50)
  - Various 8x10s of radio, television and film personalities, 1915 -- 1970; MS003.001.051.001 (Box 51)
    Unsorted, unsigned.
  - Various cabinet cards of 19th c. figures including international royalty, military figures and financiers, 1878 -- 1910; MS003.001.052.001 (Box 52)
    Unsorted, includes Queen Victoria and family, Henry Ward Beecher and Wendell Phillips.
  - Various cabinet cards of 19th c. figures including international royalty, military and financiers, 1880 -- 1910; MS003.001.053.001 (Box 53)
    Unsorted, includes Princess Victoria of Wales and some of Bruckmann's Collection of historical figures.
  - Large boudoir prints 7 1/2" x 13", actresses, actors and American presidents, MS003.001.054
    Two signed.
    - President Grover Cleveland, MS003.001.054.00001 (Box 54)
    - President James A. Garfield, MS003.001.054.00002 (Box 54)
    - President James A. Garfield, MS003.001.054.00003 (Box 54)
    - President James A. Garfield, MS003.001.054.00004 (Box 54)
    - Mrs. G.H. Gilbert, English actress, MS003.001.054.00005 (Box 54)
    - Joseph Jefferson as Caleb Plummer in "The Cricket on the Hearth," n.d., MS003.001.054.00006 (Box 54)
    - Maggie Mitchell, American actress, MS003.001.054.00007 (Box 54)
    - Maggie Mitchell, American actress, MS003.001.054.00008 (Box 54)
    - Minnie Madden Fiske, American actress, MS003.001.054.00009 (Box 54)
    - Henry Dixey, American Actors as Adonis, MS003.001.054.00010 (Box 54)
    - Sarah Bernhardt, French actress, as Camille, MS003.001.054.00011 (Box 54)
    - Edwin Booth, American actor as Hamlet, MS003.001.054.00012 (Box 54)
    - Edwin Booth, American actor, MS003.001.054.00013 (Box 54)
    - Lotta Crabtree, American actress, MS003.001.054.00014 (Box 54)
    - Mary Anderson, American actress, MS003.001.054.00015 (Box 54)
    - Lillie Langtry, English actress, MS003.001.054.00016 (Box 54)
    - Lotta Crabtree, American actress, MS003.001.054.00017 (Box 54)
    - Kyrle Bellow, English actor as Marc Antony, MS003.001.054.00018 (Box 54)
    - Mrs. Leslie Carter, American actress, MS003.001.054.00019 (Box 54)
    - Benoit Coquelin, French actor as Mascarille in "Le Precieuses Ridicules," n.d., MS003.001.054.00020 (Box 54)
    - James Lewis, as Guinnion in "The Squire," n.d., MS003.001.054.00021 (Box 54)
    - Lotta Crabtree, American actress, MS003.001.054.00022 (Box 54)
      Signed.
    - Fanny Davenport, American actress, MS003.001.054.00023 (Box 54)
    - Fanny Davenport, American actress, MS003.001.054.00024 (Box 54)
    - Clara Morris, Canadian actress, MS003.001.054.00025 (Box 54)
    - Cora Urquhart Potter, American actress as Cleopatra, MS003.001.054.00026 (Box 54)
    - John T. Raymond, American actor as Rip Van Winkle in "Walfert's Roost," n.d., MS003.001.054.00027 (Box 54)
    - Ada Rehan, Irish actress, MS003.001.054.00028 (Box 54)
    - Lawrence Barrett, American actor, MS003.001.054.00029 (Box 54)
    - Maurice Barrymore, English actor, MS003.001.054.00030 (Box 54)
    - General Hancock, MS003.001.054.00031 (Box 54)
    - Sarah Bernhardt, French actress, MS003.001.054.00032 (Box 54)
    - Lillian Russell, American actress, MS003.001.054.00033 (Box 54)
    - Lillian Russell, American actress, MS003.001.054.00034 (Box 54)
  - Group portrait of Adelina Patti's Farewell concert tour, signed, 1903 -- 1904; MS003.001.055.001 (Box 55)
    Framed 8 1/2 x 11"
  - Oversized lithographs and engravings of 19th century actors and actresses, 1870 -- 1990; MS003.001.056
    - Johanna Gadski, MS003.001.056.00001 (Box 56)
      Two images.
    - John McCormack, banquet program, MS003.001.056.00002 (Box 56)
    - Edwin Forrest (1806-72), 1870 -- 1990; MS003.001.056.00003 (Box 56)
      Various souvenir images and clippings of his career.
    - Actors and Actresses in Shakespearean and other roles, 1890 -- 1900; MS003.001.056.00004 (Box 56)
    - Various lithographs of opera figures, 1920; MS003.001.056.00005 (Box 56)
      Fowle, Frank E.
  - Large photos of actors, actresses and musical personalities, most signed, 1893 -- 1933; MS003.001.057
    - Marion Clarke, American soprano as Desdemona in Otello, MS003.001.057.00001 (Box 57)
    - Carmen Melis, Italian soprano as Thais, 1912; MS003.001.057.00002 (Box 57)
      Signed
    - Florence Hinkle, American soprano, 1923; MS003.001.057.00003 (Box 57)
      Wife of Herbert Witherspoon, signed.
    - Lucrezia Bori, Spanish soprano, as Minnie in La Boheme, 1923; MS003.001.057.00004 (Box 57)
    - Marcella Sembrich, 1923; MS003.001.057.00005 (Box 57)
    - Unidentified, MS003.001.057.00006 (Box 57)
    - Unidentified, MS003.001.057.00007 (Box 57)
    - Lilius Waldegrave, 1909 -- 1910; MS003.001.057.00008 (Box 57)
    - Tyrone Power, English actor, 1928; MS003.001.057.00009 (Box 57)
    - Guiseppe Bamboschek, Italian conductor, 1929; MS003.001.057.00010 (Box 57)
    - Jeska Swartz Morse, American contralto, MS003.001.057.00011 (Box 57)
    - Berta Morena, German soprano, 1924; MS003.001.057.00012 (Box 57)
    - Luca Botta, Italian tenor as Pinkerton in Mme Butterfly, 1917; MS003.001.057.00013 (Box 57)
    - Josef Stransky, Czech conductor, MS003.001.057.00014 (Box 57)
    - Ethel Leginska, English pianist and conductor, 1933; MS003.001.057.00015 (Box 57)
    - Roselina Galli, Italian danseuse, MS003.001.057.00016 (Box 57)
      Sgned.
    - Zelie De Lucca, MS003.001.057.00017 (Box 57)
    - William Russell, 1893; MS003.001.057.00018 (Box 57)
      Signed on back.
    - Maud B. Booth, MS003.001.057.00019 (Box 57)
    - Florencio Constantino, Spanish tenor, 1911; MS003.001.057.00020 (Box 57)
    - Hazel Dawn, MS003.001.057.00021 (Box 57)
      Attached signature.
    - Unidentified, MS003.001.057.00022 (Box 57)
      "Thy Will be Done written in English" and Latin on front.
    - Unidentified as Shylock, MS003.001.057.00023 (Box 57)
    - Unidentified, MS003.001.057.00024 (Box 57)
      Four portraits of the same person.
    - Marcella Sembrich, 1912 -- 1913; MS003.001.057.00025 (Box 57)
  - Oversize prints, photographs and posters of singers and theatrical personalities, 1882 -- 1939; MS003.001.058
    Unsorted, some signed.
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra, George Henschel, Conductor, 1882; MS003.001.058.00001 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Daniel Webster, MS003.001.058.00002 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Annie Clark, 1906; MS003.001.058.00003 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Rudolph Ganz, Swiss pianist, Conductor, 1910; MS003.001.058.00004 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Bernardino Molinari, Italian conductor, signed lithograph, 1930; MS003.001.058.00005 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Unidentified artwork, MS003.001.058.00006 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Finka Milanov, 1939; MS003.001.058.00007 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Unidentified print, MS003.001.058.00008 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Unidentified, 1920; MS003.001.058.00009 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Unidentified, MS003.001.058.00010 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Alice Nielson, handcolored picture board, MS003.001.058.00011 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Rosalind Elias, RCA/Victor recording artist poster, MS003.001.058.00012 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Leonie Rysanek, RCA/Victor recording artist poster, MS003.001.058.00013 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Giorgio Tozzi, RCA/Victor recording artist poster, MS003.001.058.00014 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    - Jan Peerce, RCA/Victor recording artist poster, MS003.001.058.00015 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)